[{"answer": "I noticed she's big on the phrase", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Yada-Yada.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": "No,", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": "Is", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Yada-Yada.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": "She is succinct", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": "What are you talking about? That marriage ended six months ago. She's already remarried", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Yada-Yada.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": "Anyway, my friend and her new husband my friend have listed me a reference for an adoption agency. They're trying to get a baby.", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": "Well, you too seem to have the same taste", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Yada-Yada.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": "Well I have the same shirt", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": "If you had gotten into the backseat of the car we could've figured this whole thing out", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Yada-Yada.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": "Not for you! Who holds a door open for a man", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": "Yeah, why should we knock ourselves out", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Yada-Yada.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": "No, no one wears the shirt next time", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": "I told you we should've gotten here a half hour early", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Yada-Yada.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": "All right, don't panic. Let's just decide now. Which one do you want", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": "All right, all right. Now what're we gonna do", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Yada-Yada.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": "All right, I'll take my friend", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": "I knew you wanted her. That's who I wanted", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Yada-Yada.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": "No, no, you think I'm fallin' for that? I'll take my friend", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": "So what're you gonna do", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Yada-Yada.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": " Hey, my friend, my friend, it's my friend. Um, thought you guys might wanna have lunch. Gimme a call. Bye", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": " No, my friend and I, we can't work it out. You know, I'm thinking of asking that my friend out by myself", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Yada-Yada.txt", "asentId": 23, "question": "I was, but the one I thought was my friend turned out to be my friend", "qsentId": 22}, {"answer": "Huh", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Yada-Yada.txt", "asentId": 25, "question": "What about all your Jewish jokes", "qsentId": 24}]